Section 1
OFFICER:
Good morning.
What can I do for you?
LOUISE:
I want to report a theft.
I had some things stolen out of my bag yesterday.
OFFICER:
I'm sorry to hear that.
Right,
so I'll need to take a few details.
Can I start with your name?
LOUISE:
Louise Taylor.
OFFICER:
OK, thank you.
And are you resident in the UK?
LOUISE:
No, I'm actually Canadian, though my mother was British.
OFFICER:
And your date of birth?
LOUISE:
December 14th, 1977.
OFFICER:
So you're just visiting this country?
LOUISE:
That's right.
I come over most summers on business.
I'm an interior designer and I come over to buy old furniture, antiques you
know.
There are some really lovely things around here,
but you need to get out to the small towns.
I've had a really good trip this year, until this happened.
OFFICER:
OK.
So you've been here quite a while?
LOUISE:
Yes, I'm here for two months.
I go back next week.
OFFICER:
So may I ask where you're staying now?
LOUISE:
Well at present I've got a place at Park Apartments,
that's on King Street.
I was staying at the Riverside Apartments on the same street,
but the apartment there was only available for six weeks
so I had to find another one.
OFFICER:
OK.
And the apartment number?
LOUISE:
Fifteen.
OFFICER:
Right.
Now, I need to take some details of the theft.
So you said you had some things stolen out of your bag?
LOUISE:
That's right.
OFFICER:
And were you actually carrying the bag when the theft took place?
Yes.
I really can't understand it.
I had my backpack on.
And I went into a supermarket to buy a few things
and when I opened it up my wallet wasn't there.
OFFICER:
And what did your wallet have in it?
LOUISE:
Well, fortunately I don't keep my credit cards in that wallet - I keep
them with my passport in an inside compartment in my backpack.
But there was quite a bit of cash there...about ￡250 sterling, I should
think.
I withdrew ￡300 from my account yesterday,
but I did a bit of shopping,
so I must have already spent about ￡50 of that.
OFFICER:
OK.
LOUISE:
At first I thought, oh I must have left the wallet back in the
apartment,
but then I realised my phone had gone as well.
It was only a week old,
and that's when I realised I'd been robbed.
Anyway at least they didn't take the keys to my rental car.
OFFICER:
Yes.
So you say the theft occurred yesterday?
LOUISE:
Yes.
OFFICER:
So that was September the tenth.
And do you have any idea at all of where
or when the things might possibly have been stolen?
LOUISE:
Well at first I couldn't believe it because the bag had been on my
back ever since I left the apartment after lunch.
It's just a small backpack,
but I generally use it when I'm travelling because it seems safer than a
handbag.
Anyway, I met up with a friend,
and we spent a couple of hours in the museum.
But I do remember that as we were leaving there, at about 4 o'clock,
a group of young boys ran up to us,
and they were really crowding round us,
and they were asking us what time it was, then all of a sudden
they ran off.
OFFICER:
Can you remember anything about them?
LOUISE:
The one who did most of the talking was wearing a T-shirt with a
picture of something...let's see...
a tiger.
OFFICER:
Right.
Any idea of how old he might have been?
LOUISE:
Around twelve years old?
OFFICER:
And can you remember anything else about his appearance?
LOUISE:
Not much.
He was quite thin...
OFFICER:
Colour of hair?
LOUISE:
I do remember that - he was blond.
All the others were dark-haired.
OFFICER:
And any details of the others?
LOUISE:
Not really.
They came and went so quickly.
OFFICER:
Right.
So what I'm going to do now is give you a crime reference number
so you can contact your insurance company.
So this is ten digits:
87954 82361
LOUISE:
Thank you.
So should I ...